[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "ஒழுங்கீனம்",
    "answers": ["ஒழுங்கீனம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "அந்திப்பொழுது",
    "answers": ["அந்திப்பொழுது"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "தெருவோரம்",
    "answers": ["தெருவோரம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "நையப்புடை",
    "answers": ["நையப்புடை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "ஊர்க்காவலர்",
    "answers": ["ஊர்க்காவலர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "முருங்கைக்காய்",
    "answers": ["முருங்கைக்காய்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "துயிலெழு",
    "answers": ["துயிலெழு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "கயிற்றாட்டம்",
    "answers": ["கயிற்றாட்டம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "மின்தூக்கி",
    "answers": ["மின்தூக்கி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "பந்து",
    "answers": ["பந்து", "கைப்பந்து"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "படிக்கட்டு",
    "answers": ["படிக்கட்டு", "படி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "மூக்குக்கண்ணாடி",
    "answers": ["மூக்குக்கண்ணாடி", "கண்ணாடி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "பொத்தான்",
    "answers": ["பொத்தான்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "கால்சட்டை",
    "answers": ["கால்சட்டை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "சுவர்",
    "answers": ["சுவர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "வியர்வை",
    "answers": ["வியர்வை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "செடி",
    "answers": ["செடி", "புதர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "சிரிப்பு",
    "answers": ["சிரிப்பு", "புன்னகை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "பேராற்றல்",
    "answers": ["பேராற்றல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "அரசகட்டளை",
    "answers": ["அரசகட்டளை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "கீழ்த்தளம்",
    "answers": ["கீழ்த்தளம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "பரப்பளவு",
    "answers": ["பரப்பளவு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "அகமகிழ்ச்சி",
    "answers": ["அகமகிழ்ச்சி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "கீழ்ப்படிதல்",
    "answers": ["கீழ்ப்படிதல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "பெருமிதம்",
    "answers": ["பெருமிதம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "இசைக்கருவி",
    "answers": ["இசைக்கருவி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "பயனீட்டாளர்",
    "answers": ["பயனீட்டாளர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "கரையோரம்",
    "answers": ["கரையோரம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "அணைக்கட்டு",
    "answers": ["அணைக்கட்டு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "செந்நிறம்",
    "answers": ["செந்நிறம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "பறைசாற்று",
    "answers": ["பறைசாற்று"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "வேலைப்பளு",
    "answers": ["வேலைப்பளு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "பேரிரைச்சல்",
    "answers": ["பேரிரைச்சல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "பண்டமாற்று",
    "answers": ["பண்டமாற்று"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
